Shall I make some coffee, Jane?
我来煮点咖啡好吗,Jane?
That's a good idea, Charlotte.
这是个好主意,Charlotte.
It's ready.
咖啡好了,
Do you want any milk?
你要放点奶吗?
Just a little, please.
请稍加一点.
What about some sugar?
加些糖怎么样?
Two teaspoonfuls?
两茶匙行吗?
No, less than that.
不,再少一些.
One and a half teaspoonfuls, please.
请放一勺儿半.
That's enough for me.
那对我足够了.
That was very nice.
太好了.
Would you like some more?
你要再来点吗?
Yes, please.
好的,请再来一点.
I'd like a cigarette, too.
我还想抽枝烟.
May I have one?
可以给我一枝吗?
Of course.
当然可以.
I think there are a few in that box.
我想那个盒子里有一些.
I'm afraid it's empty.
我恐怕盒子是空的.
What a pity!
真遗憾!
It doesn't matter.
没关系.
Have a biscuit instead.
那就吃块饼干吧.
Eat more and smoke less!
多吃点,少抽点!
That's very good advice!
这是极好的忠告啊!